Still nothing...
(カカシ)まだか!?
(ヤマト)失敗だったんでしょうか？
Could it have failed?
いや 手応えは 確かにあった。
No, there definitely was an impact.
But nothing's happening...
(いの)でも 何も起こらないわ
ヒナタ 何か見えないの？
Hinata, can you see anything?
N-No... Not even with my Byakugan...
(ヒナタ)え ええ
白眼でも そこまでは。
Naruto... Naruto won't come back?
(サクラ)ナルトは
ナルトは戻ってこないの？
Did it reach Naruto?
《ナルトたちのところまで
届かなかったのか？
しかも 三尾を
目覚めさせてしまったらしい》
Furthermore, it seems to have awakened
the Three-Tails.
Shizune!
シズネ！
(シズネ)封印班
三尾出現に備えるわよ！
Sealing team!
Standby for the Three-Tails!
Right!
(３人)はい！
サイ！
Sai!
幽鬼丸を 安全なところに頼む。
(サイ)はい。
Take Yuukimaru to a safe place.
Right!
行こう。
- Let's go.
- No!
(幽鬼丸)イヤだ 紅蓮さんが
帰ってくるまで ここにいる！
I'm staying here until Guren-san returns!
(サクラ)きっと大丈夫。
え？
I'm sure she's all right.
Huh?
みんな ナルトのことを思ってるから。
We're all thinking of Naruto,
that's why he'll return here.
ナルトは ここに帰ってくる。
あなたが思ってれば
そこに紅蓮も帰ってくるわ 必ず。
If you think of her, Guren will return too.
No doubt about it.
さあ。
Now then...
うん。
Okay.
Go!
いけ！
We will begin
the Four-Corner Sealing Jutsu.
結界四方封陣 縛の術式をとる。
Four-Corner Sealing Barrier...
結界四方封陣 縛！
Bind!
問題は ここからだな。
The challenge starts now...
Until the Sealing team has
the Three-Tails,
封印班が三尾を捕らえるまで
オレたちで抑えることになるが。
it's up to us to suppress it.
さて 三尾相手に
ボクの木遁が どこまで通じますか。
Now then, we'll see just how well
my Wood Style works
against the Three-Tails.
All we can do is try...
ま やれるだけ やるっきゃないね。
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
the "impulses" that makes you want to meet it
aitaku naru no shoudou
the "innocence" that makes you want to cry
nakitaku naru no junjou
they've gone into the summer fire
natsu no hi ni tobikonda
the fireflies aren't coming back
hotaru wa kaeranai
you didn't say a single word and left a kiss for me behind
anata wa nanimo iwazu kuchizuke wo nokoshite
and nodded as you still got burned
kitsuzuku mama unazuita ne
it was so sad that my life was wavering
kanashii hodo inochi yurameiteita
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
sha la la my sweet lovely dear
sha la la itoshiki hito
I can also see you right now
anata mo mieteiru no
the dazzling moon will softly
mabayui tsuki ga sotto
illuminate the morning day
ashita wo terashite
and strongly and strongly shine on
tsuyoku tsuyoku kagayaite
Counterattack of
the Curse Mark
ここで待とう いいね？
We'll wait here. All right?
うん ふ～。
Okay.
飲んで 疲れがとれる。
え？
Drink... It will ease your fatigue.
お兄さん わかるんだ
ボクの思ってること。
Onii--san, you can tell what I'm thinking...
みんなには 空気が読めないって
言われるけど。
Everyone tells me that
I can't read their moods.
そんなことないよ きっと。
I doubt that. Really...
はあ フフ。
(鬼鳳)魔煙丸！
Dark Smoke Sphere
Stay hidden, okay?
隠れているんだ いいね。
うん。
Okay.
(濡羅吏)粘水塊！
Water Shield Shot!
ヘッ！
(鬼霧)フフフフッ…。
かくれんぼかい？
Hide-and-seek, eh?
お迎えにあがったぜ お坊ちゃん。
I've come for you, laddie.
I've been able to determine
Yuukimaru's potential
(カブト)すでに 幽鬼丸の能力の
可能性と限界は確かめられた。
and the limit of his power.
しかし 木ノ葉のヤツら また
三尾を封印しようというのか。
However, the Hidden Leaf are trying
to seal the Three-Tails once again...
もし 万が一にも木ノ葉が➡
If by any chance, they are successful
in sealing the Three-Tails...
三尾の封印に
成功してしまったら…。
((大蛇丸 : サスケ君が必要なスキルを
手に入れさえすれば➡
When Sasuke achieves
the skills he needs...
転生の時期も近いわ。
The time for my reanimation will be near.
When that happens,
そうなれば
暁も 木ノ葉も邪魔なだけ。
both the Akatsuki and Leaf Village
will be a hindrance.
(今度の作戦は
そのときのための準備))
Our current operation is preparation
for when that happens.
三尾の力を暁に
利用される心配はなくなるが。
We won't have to worry about
the Akatsuki using
the power of the Three Tails, but...
大蛇丸様の未来戦略に
大きな変更を余儀なくされる。
It will force a big change
in Orochimaru-sama's future strategy.
それは 防がなければ。
We must avoid that...
これを使えば
幽鬼丸を失うかもしれない。
If I use this, we may lose Yuukimaru...
However, rather than lose
the Three-Tails...
しかし三尾そのものを失うよりは。
例え 幽鬼丸を
失ってもかまうものか。
Never mind... if I lose Yuukimaru!
幽鬼丸の最後の
力を使って 三尾を暴れさせ➡
I'll use Yuukimaru's remaining power
to make the Three-Tails go wild,
木ノ葉の忍どもを蹴散らしてやる。
and destroy the Leaf Ninja...!
カブトは？
(鱗児)フン。
Where's Kabuto...?
Huh, I heard everything.
オレが すべて聞いておいた。
ウフフ…！
メガネ君はいないんだ。
So Four-Eyes isn't here?
フッ！ それじゃあ
オレたちに命令するヤツは➡
So there's no one to give us orders...
いねえってわけだねぇ！
あ？
オレたちゃ 昔の
オレたちじゃねえってことさ。
We're not the same as before.
もう アンタとつるむ必要も
なくなっちゃったし。
There's no need to hang
around you anymore...
Well, it looks that way...
ま そういうことだ。
いい気なもんだぜ。
You guys are so easygoing.
何!?
What...?
所詮 テメエらは
利用されてなんぼの捨て駒だ。
You guys are just cast-offs...
pawns who are no longer useful.
And you don't even know that
I've got you in a vital spot.
まんまと急所を
握られてるってのに➡
気づきもしねえってか!?
クッ！
Say that again!
言わせておきゃ！
アンタもう➡
You're not one of us anymore!
オレたちの仲間じゃねえ！
ここで➡
Want to settle it now?
始末してやってもいいのよ。
始末？
Settle?
フッ フフフフ… アハハハ…！
なんだ 何がおかしい！
What?! What's so funny?!
クククク… そろそろのはずだぜ！
It's about time!
なんだか 体が変だよ！
What...?! My body feels strange...
ふ 震えが止まらねえ！
I can't stop shaking...
おい どうした!?
Hey, what's happening?!
グワッ！ ああっ!!
バカめ!!
Fools!
力を得るためには
リスクが伴うと知れ！
You should know that
there's a risk to attaining power!
I heard your power has
some side effects!
お前たちの力には
副作用があるって話だぜ！
ふ 副作用だぁ!?
そうさ。
Side effects...?!
Yeah...
And left alone, it will eat you up
from the inside out.
放っときゃ 体の内部から
崩れちまうんだとさ！
N-No... I don't want that to happen!
い いやよ！ そんなの!!
そ そんな… 死にたくねえ！
N-No way... I don't want to die!
フンッ！ 定期的に
カブトから薬をもらわねえと➡
Unless you get the drug from Kabuto
before the time limit,
you'll destroy yourselves
with your own power!
お前たちは お前たち自身の力で
破滅するんだよ！
カブトから預かっている！
Kabuto entrusted the drug to me.
If you say you won't betray
Orochimaru-sama,
大蛇丸様を
裏切らないっていうんなら➡
I just may give it to you.
くれてやるがな！
わかった… 忠誠を誓う。
All right. I swear my loyalty.
H-Hurry... give me the drug.
は 早く薬を！
思い知れ！ お前たちは
どう足掻いたって➡
Know this! No matter how hard you try,
you will never be able to escape
Orochimaru-sama's grasp.
大蛇丸様の掌の上からは
逃げられないんだよ！
カブトが言っていた。
Kabuto said this...
三尾の動きを止めた➡
We've stopped
the Three-Tails' movements.
And he wants to see that
power once more.
あの力をもう一度
見せてほしいってな。
いやだ！
No!
When I take that medicine,
my head feels like it's going to burst...
あの薬を飲むと
頭が割れるように痛くなる。
黙れ！ 拒むことは許さない！
Shut up! You will not refuse!
まだ紅蓮は
戻ってきていない。
Guren hasn't returned yet!
And maybe, she'll never return!
永遠に戻らないかも
しれないんだぞ!?
Do you want that?!
それでもいいのか!?
いやだ…。
No... No!
いやだよぉ！
だったら➡
Then stop being fussy and do as I say!
つべこべ言わず
オレの言うとおりにしろ!!
う うん。 もう一度…。
O-Okay... One more time.
Just one more time...
本当に もう一度だけだよ。
ああ！ それで最後だ！
Yeah... this is the last time.
くるか。
Here it comes...
おっ！
(カカシ)サイの使いか。
Is that from Sai?
どうやら 紅蓮の仲間の忍が
パワーアップし サイを襲ったらしい。
It seems Guren's fellow Ninja have
powered up and attacked Sai.
えっ!?
キバたちからの連絡は？
Huh?!
Any word from Kiba and the rest?
いえ まだ…。
No, not yet.
(シノ)まさか…。
No way...
(赤丸)バウ…。
赤丸 助かったぜ。
Akamaru, you saved me...
お前の機転で
地面に潜ってなきゃ オレたち…。
If we hadn't hidden underground
due to your quick thinking...
ク～ン…。
リー… テンテン！
Lee... Tenten...?
まさか アイツら…。
They couldn't have...!
すまん 赤丸… 大丈夫だ。
Thank you, Akamaru... I'm okay.
(キバ)お前ら 無事だったんだな！
You're all okay.
(テンテン)全然 無事じゃないわよ。
Not at all.
巻物から防御壁を
呼び出してなきゃ やられてたわ。
If I didn't summon a protection Wall
from my scroll,
we'd have been goners...
リーのヤツ 闇雲に突っ込んでいくし。
Lee was no help, rushing in like that...
(リー)くっ… 悔しいです…。
I-I'm mortified...
ガイ先生からも 常々 慢心は
忍者の敵といわれていたのに…。
After Guy-sensei often warned me
that pride is a Ninja's enemy...
まさか アイツらが
あんなにやるとはね。
I didn't expect it...
That they'd be so strong.
(キバ)いや。
No...
あの変わりようは
ただごとじゃねえ。
That transformation isn't normal.
We must notify everyone!
早いとこ みんなに知らせねえと。
ええ。
Yes...
(シノ)この霧…。
This fog... We're already in their trap...
オレたちは すでに
ヤツらの術中にいる。
封印班を守るんだ。
はい！
Protect the Sealing team!
Right!
魔煙丸！
Dark Smoke Sphere!
粘水塊！
Water Shield Shot!
ヤマト！
はい。
- Yamato!
- Right!
木遁 樹界壁！
Wood Style: Giant Forest!
この… 邪魔しやがって!!
Why you--! Getting in the way!
木遁 大樹林の術！
Wood Style: Giant Forest Jutsu!
くっ…。
寄壊蟲！
Parasitic Insect!
ん!? なに？
What? Hey, stop!
ちょっと！ イヤだ！ イヤー!!
Nooo!
おりゃ!!
ぐはっ！
どうした？ 赤丸！
みんな止まれ！ 様子が変だ！
What's wrong, Akamaru?!
Everyone, stop!
Something's strange here.
敵ですか!?
いや これは…。
The enemy?!
No... This is...
(テンテン)どう見ても
敵ではなさそうね。
It doesn't look like the enemy at all...
(リー)テンテン 赤丸君の気持が
読めるんですか!?
Tenten! You can tell
what Akamaru is feeling?!
あっ！ サイ!!
Sai!
ほう… この霧は 三尾の。
This is the Three-Tails' fog...
まだ封印は 完了していないな。
The sealing isn't complete yet.
あっ… 来るよ！
アイツが来る！
It's coming...! It's coming!
チャクラを集中させて！
はい！
Gather your Chakra!
了解！
しゃ～んなろ～！
- Yes!
- Right!
Shannaro!
来たか！
Here it comes!
(鱗児)飲むんだ 幽鬼丸！
えっ！
Swallow it, Yuukimaru.
全部 飲むんだ！
紅蓮に帰ってきてほしいんだろ？
Huh?!
Swallow all of it!
You want Guren to return, don't you?
わかった！ ボクやるよ！
Okay, I'll do it.
紅蓮さんのいるところが
ボクの帰る場所だから。
Because the place
I'll return to is where Guren is...
(紅蓮)うっ あっ…。
戻れたのか…。
I made it back...
うっ あっ…。
痛いってことは
まだ生きてるってことだな。
Feeling pain means I'm still alive.
あっ！
(紅蓮)ナルト…。
Naruto...
起きろ！ ナルト！
うっ…。
Wake up! Naruto!
幽鬼丸… 無事だったか？
Yuukimaru... you're okay?
寝ぼけている場合じゃないだろ！
ん？
This is no time to babble in your sleep!
うわっ！
オレたち 戻れたのか？
ああ。
We made it back...?
Yeah...
幽鬼丸… 幽鬼丸！ どこだ!?
Yuukimaru... Where's Yuukimaru?!
(鬼霧)フフフフッ… ハハハハ！
煙重分身。
Multi-Smoke Clone.
イヤ～ やめて！
あぁ あぁ～！
No... Stop!
ウフフフフフ。
くすぐった～い。
なに!?
It tickles...
What?!
あらあら あなたの
かわいい蟲さんたちも形無しね。
Oh dear... Your cute little bugs
are shapeless now.
それじゃあ 本番いくわよ
はっ！
Well, now for the main show.
Here I come!
うっ！
フフ。
おもしれえ
こいつはいただきだ！
This is interesting...
I'm taking this!
出でよ 煙龍！
Arise Smoke Dragon!
あっ！ あ あ…。
《サイが伝えてきたとおり➡
Like Sai reported...
以前のコイツらとは
まるで別人だな》
they're totally different from before.
うぅ…！
うっ！
シズネ先輩！
Sh-Shizune-Senpai...!
いのは限界か しかし…。
Ino has reached her limit... But...
いの なんとか持ち堪えて！
Ino! Just hang in there!
Shizune-sama...
No way! Not that power again!
Yuukimaru!
before the reality of a deep breath
sonzai to shinkokyuu no genjitsu wo mae ni
my gaze my very existence tries to challenge it
idomou to suru shisen wa
mistakes are made and in the confusion of it all everything burns into my mind
machigai mo tomadoi mo zenbu yaki tsukeru
in a series of moments
isshun no renzoku no naka de
beyond a great number of promises
ikutsu mono yakusoku no sono ue ni tatte wa
are the words that spilled over from the day as I reflect upon them
kamishimeru ano hi koboreochita kotoba
it's as though I made a vow which expresses these feelings into words
komerareta omoi wa chikai no you de
then it would link the befinning with the present day
kuchi ni sureba ima to hajimari wo tsunagu
it's not in my dreams
yume de wa nakute
that place doesn't exist in a fantasy world either
esoragoto no sekai de mo nai basho de sa
before the reality of a deep breath
sonzai to shinkokyuu no genjitsu no mae ni
my gaze my very existence tries to challenge it
idomou to suru shisen wa
mistakes are made and in the confusion of it all everything burns into my mind
machigai mo tomadoi mo zenbu yaki tsukete
embracing the long path ahead
sono zutto saki wo toraeru
in a series of moments
isshun no renzoku no naka de
Next Episode
Yuukimaru may not forgive me
when he finds out... the whole truth.
Are you still mulling over that?
≪(カツユ)シズネ様…。
I'm prepared to protect Yuukimaru, but...
If I were you, I'd keep thinking of him!
Even if I'm despised, or rejected...
or resented!
うわぁ～!!
Whether he thinks that
I'm the place to return to or not...
has nothing to do with it!
Yeah, you're right!
I'll become the fool too... just like you.
まさか また あの力を？
幽鬼丸！
Next time: "Memory of Guilt"
Memory of Guilt
昆虫採集が趣味だという
油女シノ君。
"YAMATO'S ROOM"
Aburame Shino-kun,
who loves to collect insects...
今日のお客様です。
is our guest today.
さっそくですが シノ君は
木ノ葉でも有数の一族である➡
Getting right to the point...
Shino-kun, you're a member of the prominent
Aburame family in Leaf Village,
油女一族のご出身で
いつもクールにきめてるけど➡
ご家族の皆さんも
そうなんですか？
and you're always calm and cool.
Is the rest of your family like you?
寡黙であること すなわち…。
Silence. Namely...
なるほど 寡黙は つまり
体内に宿している蟲たちとの➡
I see. Silence signifies that
you are communicating
対話を意味すると
そういうことですね。
with the insects you host
inside your bodies?
ああ。
生まれたときから➡
Yes...
なにか特別なことを
されるそうですが。
I understand that in the Aburame family,
you do something special from
the time you are born?
それは 一族の秘術として…。
That is a secret family Jutsu...
体の中に蟲を寄生させて➡
From the time you are born,
you host insects inside your body,
ご自身のチャクラを与えることで
共存していると➡
sustain them with your Chakra,
and co-exist.
簡単に言えば
こういうことですね。
ああ。
Is that a simple way of putting it?
その蟲たちを使って 追尾 治癒
分身などを行う秘伝術こそが➡
Yes...
And you use the insects in
your secret Jutsu to do things
秘術なんですね。
ああ。
like tracking, healing and cloning.
And that is your secret family Jutsu,
is that correct?
ちょっと見せてもらえません？
ここで!?
Yes...
Can you demonstrate for us?
できなければ結構ですけど。
Here...?
It's okay if you can't.
時間がないので
ちゃっちゃと やってください。
We're running out of time,
so please do it quickly.
では…。
おっと 時間です。
Well then...
Oops! It's already time.
Our guest was Aburame Shino-kun.
今日のお客様 油女シノ君でした。
(シノ)もう終わり…。
It's... over already...?